Looks like it's working!
What floor do you want to go to? #Y
You arrived at the 1st Floor.
The power's not on.
You examined the register.
You examined the locker.
There's nothing special.
Hmm? I found something!
It's just trash.
Jiro is excited.
It was just your imagination.
It looks broken.
It feels hard. It doesn't look like you can expect a good sleep.
"For some reason, the ancient machine seems to make you want to sing."
It's a bell. Looks like they had bells in ancient times as well.
This switch opens the door.
This switch turns on the lights.
3F
2F
Cancelar
What's this?
Bzzzzz 
You... have... the brain of a monkey... Hee hee hee!
Hmph.
Grrr! You stupid machine!
Shu... You really are like a monkey.
"Oh, shut up! Why don't you give it a try, then!"
Bzzzzz 
"In ten years, you'll be as bald as an egg... Hee hee hee."
I knew it...
Ha ha ha! It's right about that!
"This thing is mean... Now it's your turn, Kluke."
Bzzzzz.
You'll be flat-chested your whole life! Hee hee hee. 
Boing! 
Whirr... Clunk...
...
...
What?
"It's broken, and it no longer runs."
"For some reason, you feel like singing. Everyone's MP is replenished."
"It's soft, fluffy, and calming. Everyone's HP is replenished."
Está trancada.
It's already unlocked.
It's blocked by a barrier.
"If this is an ancient hospital, don't you think we should look around?"
Why? 
"There are probably monsters, and they might have something we can use. "
"Wow, Shu! Did you think of that all by yourself? "
Shut up! Quit makin' fun of me! 
Shu! Wait a second! 
Hmm? What's wrong? 
There's something about this machine. 
"This machine, huh... "
Shu! You're going to break it! 
I'm not gonna break it. Hmmm... this looks like I can... 
Click. 
Wh-wha--?! Shu!
Are you two Okay? 
I don't really feel anything wrong.
"Me, neither. "
"Shu, we don't know what these things do, so don't just go pushing buttons! "
"Sorry, sorry. But you know, I feel kinda good! "
"Now that you mention it, so do I. It seems to have healed us. "
The machine did that? 
"I think it might have. If we get hurt, let's try using this device. "
You pushed the light switch.
"Shu, you okay? "
"Good. Quit making me worry, Shu."
Your wounds are... healed?
Seems so...
It looks like this machine can heal us whenever we get hurt. 
Let me see?
