Swallow the Light Sphere? #Y
Yes
No
Got: Light Sphere
Open the door and move on.
Open the door and return to the Great Hall.
You used the light sphere. Now you can control the mechat. 
Escape!
Wow!
Incredible...
My shadow is...!?
Let's go farther in.
I ain't running from nobody!
We don't have time for this!
"All right, all right! If we're gonna run, then let's run!"
"What are you waiting for? Quickly, swallow the light sphere and escape from here!"
It's too dangerous ahead! You can escape in the mechat. Hurry!
You can't climb down. The bottom of the ladder is broken off.
It's bent and jammed shut.
