Exit to the surface? #Y
I think we can get it working!
Use the elevator? #Y
Ride the conveyor belt? #Y
I think we can get it working!
Push the switch? #Y
The conveyor belt started moving in reverse.
Hmm... It doesn't look like it works. 
Too bad the conveyor belt isn't moving in the other direction. 
Let's go back and see if we can find something.
It won't open!
The power's not on.
I think we can get it working!
Turn on the switch? #Y
The automatic door started working!
The power switch for the automatic door is on.
There's a Red Skeleton guarding it.
There's a Lazy Spine Ghost guarding it.
There's a Goblin Crab guarding it.
I bet this is the part for the laser device.
"Okay, let's get back to the surface, quick!"
Return to the surface? #Y
A burst of cold air blasted out. Everyone's HP went down a little.
