"Something is being displayed, but Shu and the others can't understand it."
You've never seen a machine like this before. It's working busily.
This is the elevator switch.
This is the door switch.
"You tried to turn the wheel, but it was stuck and wouldn't budge."
It won't open!
I do hear somebody inside. Maybe it is locked from somewhere else.
Do you want to go to Floor 2A? #Y
Do you want to go to Floor 2B? #Y
Were those robots always that weak? 
"No, we've gotten strong. "
"Heh heh, yeah. I guess so."
"Well, we can ask whoever that voice is to tell us about Nene! "
This elevator goes to Floor 2A.
An indicator needle is moving.
This elevator goes to Floor 2B.
It's locked.
It's already unlocked.
You've never seen a machine like this before. It's working busily.
You almost got sucked in! Everyone's HP has been reduced a bit.
This machine looks broken.
