Você está saindo desta cidade? #Y
Eu nunca tinha visto alguém tão teimoso... Eu não poderia falar com outro ministro?
A reconstrução de Talta? A aniquilação dos monstros? Você sabe o quanto isso vai custar?
O resgate de hoje saiu bastante caro. Nós não podemos sair do teto.
Peço por favor! A aldeia tem que ser habitável.
"É inaceitável, por favor, você deveria sair agora."
"Algum dia, quando eu voltar para a vila, vou deixá-la tão bonita."
Paruto! Eu não vi você desde que saímos da Vila de Talta. O que faz aqui?
Kluke... É que o jardim é tão lindo que...
"Eu estou apenas chocado, eu não tenho a menor idéia de como eles fizeram este jardim tão bonito."
Eu acredito que a sala do trono está no andar mais alto. Mas eles não vão deixar você entrar sem uma audiência.
Morizon! O que você está fazendo aqui?
Eu estava olhando o retrato do Rei Jibral.
O rei é tão legal quanto Maro!
"O rei é jovem, mas governa bem. Ele ajudará a todos, sem dúvida."
A família real de Jibral possui muito podere.
Este castelo é tão grande quanto eu imaginava... seria maravilhoso morar em um lugar como este.
Com certeza é um castelo maravilhoso. Bom que eu vivi muito tempo para ver isso!
O cavalo do rei é legal! Eu quero me juntar aow Mestres da Espada algum dia!
Shu! Olhe este grande jardim!
"Coluti! O que você está fazendo aqui? Isso não é Talta, então se comporte!"
Sim senhor! Heh heh heh... estava imitando os Mestres da Espada!
Me siga!
Os Mestres da Espada são os guardas do rei.
Nosso atual líder é Lady Zola. Ela é uma capitã fabulosa.
Os Mestres da Espada também descansam.
Ninguém sabe de onde veio Lady Zola.
"Não diga, mas há uma arma secreta escondida aqui."
O cara ao meu lado é um pouco estranho. É melhor ignorá-lo.
Relinchar!
Eu sou o chefe de cozinha do rei. Todos aqui são meus assistentes.
"Ei! Posso ajudá-lo? Você precisa de algo da cozinha, senhor?"
Eu apenas cheirei algo realmente delicioso.
Ho ho ho... Você terá a chance de um dia provar meus pratos.
É algo que você pode esperar.
Eu sou o primeiro assistente do chefe de cozinha. Eu posso cozinhar tão perfeitamente quanto o meu mestre.
Eu sou o segundo assistente do chefe de cozinha. Eventualmente todos nós parecemos se assemelhar a ele.
Eu sou apenas um assistente aqui. Mas vou me acabar parecendo o grande chefe.
"Quanto mais eles trabalham aqui, mais se parecem com ele. Eu tento evitar o máximo possível."
"Se você tem um pedido, veja o ministro sênior. Ele deve estar em algum lugar neste andar."
Hm Eu pensei que eu tinha dito para não deixar ninguém entrar. O que você quer aqui?
Hum ...
"Sim, sim, consulte o ministro sênior para pedidos. Ele deve estar em algum lugar neste andar."
Leve suas questões triviais para o ministro sênior. Eu estou muito ocupado.
"Oh querida, agora crianças? Estou ocupado. Por favor, esteja a caminho."
Nosso chefe da aldeia estava te implorando! Por favor pense em Talta!
Basta! Estou ocupado. Leve essa conversa para o ministro sênior.
A sala do trono é um andar acima. Esses soldados vão te guiar.
Você é de Talta? As pessoas de Talta estão no castelo agora.
Este é o quarto de hóspedes. Alguns outros de Talta estão aqui agora.
Apenas pessoas selecionadas podem entrar no Castelo de Jibral.
O Castelo de Jibral é enorme. Tenha cuidado para não se perder.
Atualmente estamos discutindo uma estratégia importante.
Eu não posso dizer o que é.
Há muitas pessoas no grande salão hoje.
Eu me pergunto se vamos conseguir um aumento.
Tem havido muitos monstros ultimamente.
"Se você está indo para o andar de cima, cuidado com seus modos pelo caminho."
Não é um belo jardim?
Não é um belo jardim?
Este é o quarto de Lady Zola... Mas ela está falando com o rei agora.
Este é o quartel do ministro Jonveeno. Por favor seja educado.
O jardim central está à frente.
O jardim central está à frente.
Este é o quartel do ministro. Por favor seja educado.
Este é o quarto de espera dos Mestres da Espada.
"Você não está aqui procurando problemas, certo?"
Além desta porta é a sala do trono.
Além desta porta é a sala do trono.
Esta é a sala do trono.
Esta é a sala do trono.
Eles estão fazendo pesquisas secretas. Pessoas não autorizadas não são permitidas.
Não é magnífico! Este é o cavalo do rei.
"Se você estiver indo para o andar de cima, use a escada principal à sua frente."
Eu realizei o meu sonho ao me tornar um soldado de Jibral.
Você pode ir até o Grande Salão por esta porta.
Você pode ir até o Grande Salão por esta porta.
Meus antepassados também trabalharam para Jibral.
Este é o quarto do rei.
Por esta porta ocê pode chegar ao laboratório do porão.
Este é a sala de espera dos soldados.
O laboratório está à frente. Você deve ficar quieto.
"Há coisas interessantes no laboratório do porão. Vou lhe conceder acesso, então vá e dê uma olhada."
Zola disse que ela estaria visitando o laboratório também.
O tempo da batalha está se aproximando... Preciso ver o que está acontecendo no laboratório.
Eu estou indo para o laboratório do porão. Eu vou avisá-los de que você virá.
Os Mestres da Espada são os guardas do rei.
Nosso atual líder é Lady Zola. Ela é uma capitã fabulosa.
Os Mestres da Espada também descansam.
"Você viu o porão? Se você ainda não viu, deve dar uma olhada."
"Não comente, mas há uma arma secreta escondida aqui."
O cara ao meu lado é um pouco estranho. É melhor ignorá-lo.
Relinchar!
Os Gorgos deve lutar bravamente pelo rei Jibral!
Jibral não pode fazer nada sem os Gorgos.
"Há muito lixo descartado aqui, é difícil andar por aí. Tenha cuidado."
Estamos procurando por peças para consertar o Mechat abatido.
Lady Zola está na sala dos fundos.
"Felizmente, o único dano causado ao navio que derrubamos foi o nosso ataque."
"Depois do resgate, nós o desmontamos. Agora estamos analisando seu equipamento interno na sala dos fundos."
Surprised? This is a machine called a mechat. We shot it down with a giant arrow.
"Unfortunately, the arrow launcher was destroyed by the mother ship."
That blue barrier is made from ancient technology. We're looking for a way to disable it.
"We looked through ancient books, and we found an odd technique called a Field Barrier."
It creates a barrier of light that can damage things. But you cannot gain experience by using it.
"You can only gain experience for your Shadow, your source of magic power... or so it is written."
The Eternal Engine is an ancient machine created with magic to run forever without using any fuel.
The heart of that ship is stored ahead. Our future strategy hinges on it.
The energy created with the Eternal Engine could break apart the tsunami vortex.
"We're very patient, so when you find a mystery you can come back at any time."
I am the king's chief chef. Everyone here is my assistant.
I am the chief chef's first assistant. I can cook as perfectly as my master.
I am the chief chef's second assistant. We all seem to resemble him eventually.
I'm just an assistant here. But even I ended up looking like the chief chef.
"The longer they work here, the more they resemble him. I try to avoid here as much as possible."
"The king is expecting a lot from magic, but I don't have a lot of faith in it."
Take your trivial questions to the senior minister. I am very busy.
Come see me again.
"What, you're leaving already?"
"Hey, it's the dog lover! Why are you here in the castle?"
Ho ho ho. I am a minister here in Jibral.
Say hi to the girl and the puppy.
They sure can eat!
The people from Talta have finished eating and have returned to Castle Town.
"To get to the town, go through these doors."
You're free to come and go as you please.
We're currently discussing important strategy.
I cannot say what it is.
The people from Talta have gone home already.
I wonder if we'll get a raise.
There have been a lot of monsters lately.
"If you're going upstairs, mind your manners as you go."
Isn't this a wonderful garden?
Isn't this a wonderful garden?
Lady Zola is out. She said she was going to the basement lab.
This is Minister Jonveeno's quarters. Please be polite.
The central garden is ahead.
The central garden is ahead.
This is the senior minister's quarters. Please be polite.
This is the Blademasters' waiting quarters.
"Hey, I heard you're going to participate in the strategy."
Beyond this door is the throne room..
This is the throne room.
This is the throne room.
This is the throne room.
Please go on through.
This is the lounge.
Isn't it magnificent! This is the king's horse.
That big one is a Gorgo. They're used as soldiers in Jibral.
It's time for a break.
I wonder if we'll get more breaks.
Even soldiers need breaks.
"If you're going upstairs, use the main staircase ahead of you."
I've fulfilled my dream of becoming a Jibral soldier.
You can go down to the Great Hall through this door.
You can go down to the Great Hall through this door.
Have you seen the lab?
The king returned to his quarters.
You can get to the basement lab through this door.
This is the soldiers' waiting quarters.
The lab is ahead. Please be quiet.
Lady Zola!
Lady Zola!
What?
"Take a walk about Jibral if you like. When you get tired, stop in at the inn. "
Have you seen the lab?
The king is in his quarters.
Lady Zola has returned to her quarters.
"I will leave war to men. Of course, there are women who are stronger than men."
To burst in here when I'm balancing the books! Nene knows nothing of economy.
I think my virtue is why children and dogs like me so much... Hah hah!
"Don't worry, I'll take care of the dog. Now then, to the roof! The king is waiting."
"Take this with you, then. It might be of some help."
"Don't worry, I'll take care of the dog. Now then, to the roof! The king is waiting."
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
They're busy preparing the second and third floors so don't get in the way.
"Hey, you made it. The king is waiting on the roof."
Not used
Both the king and Lady Zola are out on the roof.
It's time to battle the tsunami vortex!
"Please, go over to the king. The central garden is full with people from the Aerial Troops."
"Please, go over to the king. The central garden is full with people from the Aerial Troops."
"It's dangerous, so hide somewhere."
The Blademasters are already heading for the roof.
Those are Jibral's Aerial Troops. They are air-fighting professionals!
The king awaits you on the roof!
The king awaits you on the roof!
"Why are you here? Hurry up, to the roof!"
Leave the throne room to us. Hurry up to the roof!
What is this...? This sudden chill. Is it because of that strange purple cloud?
The one at the front of the left line is my younger brother. I hope he doesn't try to show off.
You made it. The king is waiting on the roof.
You made it. The king is waiting on the roof.
We are Jibral's air forces. We've trained for this day.
It's about to start... Who are we going to fight?
We're boarding a balloon from the central garden.
We're finally putting the long years of the king's plans into action. You should go up to the roof.
Leave this to us. You should go up to the roof.
"I'm so nervous, my heart's about to explode! But I will fight bravely."
Nothing can defeat us in the air. We are Jibral's Aerial Troops.
"First time I've seen you kids. You're the magic-users, aren't you?"
Hic! I joined in a toast a little while ago. Ha ha!
Don't worry. We have trained day in and day out for this moment.
Our plan will succeed! It must!
The future is in our hands! Failure is not an option.
I wonder if we'll fight the terrible weapons depicted on the ancient murals.
We're locked and loaded. Ready to go.
The ancient weapons are no match for Jibral's technical skills.
But what is this strange sound? It's throwing me off!
Not used
The king has already headed for the roof. He should be waiting for you.
The servants and scientists were evacuated downstairs. Many years of planning are about to pay off!
You're in the way! Move!
"Ohhh, this is the end of Jibral! I've never seen anything so horrific!"
"Don't worry about us, hurry on up to the roof."
There can be no delays. Failure is not an option!
What're you doing? Step aside!
There is something we must protect.
"All right, here we go!"
We fight as one! Get up in the balloon and fight!
"Using the balloons, huh? Good luck!"
We'll have some tales to tell after we're done with this!
With your help we successfully pulled them in! But the true battle still awaits us!
It was thanks to Shu! Good luck once you're in the balloon!
You're very powerful in spite of your size. Go sink that thing!
"Even without you, we did good. My strength, number one!"
You! Brave one!
Are you going up in the balloon? Good luck!
Are you going up in the balloon? Good luck!
The battle is about to begin! We will follow you!
"So far everything's going according to plan! I wonder, though..."
You must fight bravely. Be calm at all times.
We will be right behind you. You are the key to this battle.
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
The preparations are ready. Get in the balloon and follow the king.
Be strong. We're counting on you.
The wind is strong. Extra careful with the preparations...
One look in your eyes gave me courage. You will do well no matter what!
"It may be your first time in a balloon, but leave everything to us."
This lukewarm wind... I can't take much more of it. I hope it's over quick!
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
"This might sound like we're treating you like children, but listen carefully to Lady Zola."
"Oh, it's no good. My legs have been shaking non-stop."
"I want to fight from the balloon too! But I'm just a private, so I don't get to go."
I'm going first!
You have magic. You can't lose to ancient weapons.
"Quickly, follow the king!"
We will be right behind you. Good luck!
That base shall soon be ours. But why do I feel so nervous?
The king himself is fighting. We must help him!
Oh how calm Lady Zola appears! So regal...
Let's fight for the sake of our families!
When it gets dangerous help us with your magic!
What are you doing? Lady Zola is waiting!
How unlucky can I get! Today is my birthday!
I've never felt so nervous before. Good luck!
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
It's not over yet.
"As the head of my kingdom, it is important to celebrate, but..."
But where is Nene...
Lady Zola! What are you thinking?
Nothing Marumaro. You just keep being lighthearted.
That reminds me. The king has something he wanted to discuss with you later.
Let me know when you're about to leave. Got it?
How do you like our celebrations? Have you enjoyed the food and conversation?
Ready to leave? #Y
"All right, follow me."
Is that so? Then we'll wait a bit longer.
"Fight, eat, celebrate... Men are so simple."
"It was a long, long battle. But we finally destroyed the tsunami vortex."
"Zola was the most valiant one of all, but I'm not too pleased..."
The men are disappointing. What could they have done without you outsiders?
"If this is the end of all battles, the expense of this celebration isn't bad. If only this were really the end..."
The expenses last night alone were about half our expected military budget.
If it hadn't been for you we would have gone bankrupt.
I wonder if that puppy went straight back to the little girl.
You must be bored talking to an old man. Go and talk with the others.
I'm so glad you're safe! You did well to emerge victorious!
It was a terrible battle that could have been lost at any moment.
This is a great accomplishment! You should be proud.
Jibral can do nothing without Gorgos. Ha ha ha ha!
"Me! Fought with small guy, there!"
You! Know me? Fought with you!
The kitchen is a whirl of activity.
"You're worn out after the battle? Oh, nonsense!"
"You're young. Eat up, and you'll feel better soon."
This celebration is for you. Enjoy it at your leisure!
Eat up and feel better!
I'm so glad there weren't any major casualties...
Our lips are smacking over the good food and we're drunk on the wine of victory!
This is true happiness!
This should put an end to all the strange things happening everywhere.
It's no exaggeration to say that all our hard work was for this day.
I will never forget fighting alongside the king as long as I live.
Did you see? When the mother ship went down? I never knew victory would be so thrilling!
The Land Sharks should stop threatening Talta now. That's good.
Jibral has been saved. A toast to a magnificent king!
This is a victory to commemorate! This will be part of our great history!
Happiness to all our people!
Magic is great but it can be terrifying... You have to be careful to control your strength.
I can't drink anymore...
"Eat more, drink more, come on!"
If you hadn't been here we would never have won.
"Yes, it was electrifying."
Our king fighting in such a great battle makes me so very proud of him.
"Great job! This isn't much, but I want you to have it."
Inviting a waitress from Cafe Jibral... The king has style!
A toast to the chief chef as well!
I ate too much... I feel sick...
You'll be heroes when you go out in the streets! Well done!
A toast to our wonderful king!
That Cafe Jibral waitress is very cute.
I bet there'll be lots of presents.
There's delicious food at every table. I'm getting dizzy from looking at it all.
"Who is Nene, exactly? Is he a survivor from the ancient world?"
Of course we can't really go crazy when the king and his ministers are here.
"Right now, they are singing about your efforts in the streets!"
It's great food!
Cafe Jibral is also known as the hub of information. You can find out many things there.
The king's stock is going to go up with this battle.
I just can't calm down... Is the battle really over?
"A second ago, I shared a glance with Secretary Shuria. I wonder if she has feelings for me..."
I thought you were just children! Yet you did it!
You really outdid yourselves! Let's go to Cafe Jibral sometime!
I run Cafe Jibral. Come by sometime.
I run Cafe Jibral. I wanted to be in on the celebration.
I ran over here from Cafe Jibral! Have a good time.
You fought well. Let's fight together again.
My portion of the feast... I hope there's some left...
A battle to be remembered in history!
"The victory was thanks to Captain Zola! And you too, of course!"
The mechat you brought back is stored in the lab.
"But unfortunately the Eternal Engine was damaged, and we're not sure if we can fix it."
"Just relax! With my brains, we'll find a way to repair it!"
It's been a week since I left the lab. Am I funky?
It's been several months since I've seen food like this.
(burp) I ate too much... I ate three million calories...
Nobody ate as much as me!
(burp) I ate too much. What? Three million calories?
I ate three million and ONE calories!
Who says? I ate the most.
"Yeah, I ate three million and TWO calories!"
"Yeah, I ate three million and THREE calories!"
"Yeah, I ate three million and FOUR calories!"
"Yeah, I ate three million and FIVE calories!"
"Yeah, I ate three million and SIX calories!"
"Yeah, I ate three million and SEVEN calories!"
"Yeah, I ate three million and EIGHT calories!"
"Yeah, I ate three million and NINE calories!"
"Yeah, I ate three million and..."
"Hey, how many was it? I forgot..."
"How embarrassing... Here, take this!"
Zzz...
I drank too much.
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
We don't know what dangers await us in the lands to the north.
Be careful.
We're counting on you. We're waiting for good news.
"While Lady Zola is away, the king himself is expected to lead the Blademasters."
"Jibral, which has grown so prosperous, must now aid other lands."
Visit again the places you once knew. There may be something new there.
My superior has been a little gentler since that purple cloud appeared.
What? Even the guy next to me has a heart to love Jibral.
Not used
"Hey, brother! Visit the Alumaru Village too."
We Gorgos are a hundred times stronger than humans.
This is the mechat you brought back. It's still broken and won't work.
We have to get more parts to repair it. But we'll fix your mechat!
The mechat's Eternal Engine is still intact. It just won't run...
"Well, this is up to the head scientist. He will find some way to repair it."
"This is the mechat you brought back. It looks great, but it just won't work."
"The Eternal Engine is intact, but..."
There are too many unknowns in ancient technology.
We're thinking about how to repair the mechat. We're going to make sure it flies again.
Ancient civilization is very complex.
There's nothing we can't solve with research! I think...
It's a mystery! We're studying the mechat's mysteries!
"Oh yeah, and don't forget to collect any mysterious items you find."
"I am the chief chef here. The food at Jibral Castle is good, of course it is!"
I am the chief chef's first assistant. I can cook as perfectly as my master.
I am the chief chef's second assistant. We all seem to resemble him eventually.
I'm just an assistant here. But even I ended up looking like the chief chef.
"The longer they work here, the more they resemble him. I try to avoid here as much as possible."
The king might embark on another expedition. He has the face of someone wanting to travel.
The king is naive. We must get more taxes from the people in future.
What have we here? You have brought safety to Jibral.
You have given us this peace.
There have been no guests of late... I wonder what happened.
"You're leaving? Well, I appreciate everything. "
Come again any time!
I think I'm going to take the next Blademaster test.
There are ancient relics all over the world. But hardly anyone has ever seen them.
I shall protect this kingdom!
"No matter what happens, I'm sure you will find a way."
We are soldiers because we fight!
We will always talk about how you fought in that battle.
"It's Master Shu and his friends! Please, look about the garden at your leisure."
Please take your time.
We'll be on guard while Lady Zola is away.
This is Minister Jonveeno's quarters.
The central garden is ahead.
The central garden is ahead.
This is the senior minister's quarters.
This is the Blademasters' waiting quarters.
You can hear all sorts of gossip if you go Cafe Jibral.
This is the throne room.
This is the throne room.
This is the throne room.
This is the throne room.
Please pass!
This is the lounge.
The king is here a lot lately. He seems a little lonely...
The Gorgo beastfolk are very kind-hearted.
The soldiers gathered here are really all good-for-nothings.
I decided to quit being a soldier. It wasn't for me.
"I could take a brief rest, I guess."
"The king is a good king, but... It hurts when he is too hard on us."
"I'm glad I got to be a Jibral soldier, but reality is different than the dream."
You can go down to the Great Hall through this door.
You can go down to the Great Hall through this door.
How are your adventures going?
The king is away now.
The door to the basement lab is over there.
This is the soldiers' waiting quarters.
Are you sightseeing? The lab is up ahead.
Are your travels going well? You can come back for a rest any time.
But then there's Kluke...
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
"Had I not the duty to protect my kingdom, I would rather be going with you."
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
The king is in his quarters.
Not used
Not used
Not used
Hurry and see the head scientist in the lab. I'm counting on you.
"Have you seen the head scientist, then? Then hurry to Noluta."
Hurry and get that ancient machine started.
"Ah, you saved that frozen village, I see. That was very courageous."
Yet more good news. I heard that the people from Talta returned home safely.
The ancient machine became an azure sentinel? The Ancients' ideas were incredible!
How splendid to see all five of you like this.
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
This is the king's quarters.
Not used
Not used
Not used
Where are you going?
"You haven't suddenly lost your nerve, have you?"
"Jiro! And Shu and everyone else, too! Are you going home now?"
"The truth is, Chief Copos is visiting important people here to get aid for Talta."
Can you help him? The quarters for the king and his ministers are upstairs.
"Ah, that's right. We want to see the king again, too."
Hey!
There's an important conference in the throne room now. You can't just walk in there!
It's you! You're the dog-lover!
"Ho ho ho, you finally got here? I'm actually also a minister here."
Was there something you wanted to ask?
Please help the people of Talta! The village needs to be livable again...
"Ah, your first concern is the village? What a kind attitude. Let me propose it to the other ministers."
And you must want to meet with the king. Go upstairs to the throne room and see him.
I will show you to the throne room.
Not used
We now know a disaster will occur each year. 
"In fact, various disasters happen in other towns and villages as well."
"After what you told me, I believe these disasters and the assault on Talta village are the work of Nene."
We were traveling the world to conduct research on the various yearly disasters.
"Actually, we were on our way home when we came across you."
"Lady Zola, you'll fight with us, right?"
What'd you expect?
Whoa! She's so direct.
"But there's more to Lady Zola, Shu."
Huh?
Lady Zola is also cute when she smiles!
"We will destroy the tsunami vortex with this Eternal Engine. Once we do that, we should see the mother ship."
Awesome...
"But after that, how will we fight the mother ship?"
"Well, we'll see."
The research is coming along. It's just a matter of time.
I'm returning to my quarters. Will you join me? #Y
Hey! Maro wanna go to Lady Zola's quarters!
"Shu, we were invited here but you want to leave already?"
Let's at least talk to Zola before we leave.
"The king's calling for us, not the time to go that way!"
Not used
This is our chance to talk with Lady Zola! Let Maro stay up here a little longer!
Not used
Doesn't this dog belong to Shifa?
Why is it here?
Shifa is probably worried about... But it should be safe with the senior minister.
Hey! It's that dog!
That's the dog Shifa was looking for! It was here all along?
I'm so relieved. It should be safe with the senior minister.
"No, no! You can't! You can't come in now!"
Go see the king first. I'm very busy right now!
Oh! How good to see you again! Are your travels still going well?
"Yeah, couldn't be better! But, there's something we need your help with."
Tell me whatever you need.
The village of Noluta is frozen by an ancient machine.
The people frozen there are still alive! Please tell us how to help them.
I am very curious about that ancient machine. We have been studying it downstairs for many years now.
I've been told we are close to deciphering its code. Your information may clear things up.
"Thank you, King Jibral!"
But what happened to Zola? She's nowhere to be seen...
We were separated from Zola at Nene's base... But I'm sure she's okay.
"I see... You're right. We'll just have to trust that she'll return, then."
"Oh ho, the machine that froze the village? We were just doing research on that."
My brainpower has finally solved the mystery of the password for melting the ice.
A password? What's that?
"Simply put, it's like a spell. You can use magic, right?"
"So you should be able to use this, then. Ready? I'll only say it once."
Kirkarkla Aynayangian Modolo Moday Birol Mahayoco Shin.
"Okay, I've got it!"
"Oh-ho-ho! Young folks have such great memories, no? Go back to the village and test it out, then."
Got: Password!
I am the head scientist here. My field is all the world's mysteries.
Our duty is to study those mysteries. Is there a mystery that bothers you?
"Speaking of mysteries, that item we got at the mural village is a mystery for sure..."
"Show it to me, then."
You handed him the $C2<$I376>.
"Oh, I see. This part is used in ancient advanced technology."
"It was so powerful it was split into three parts: alpha, beta and gamma."
"When you have them all, I might be able to put them together."
He returns the $C2<$I376>.
"I am very patient, so come back whenever you find a mystery."
Hang on a bit!
I totally forgot to tell you! Zola is waiting in the back room.
Mysteries! I smell a good mystery!
"Sir, I think these three mystery items are the common parts."
Let me see...
Mysteries! I smell a good mystery!
"Sir, we found some mysterious items."
What? You brought me six?! Let me see them!
You handed him the $C2<Unknown Item>
Success! The mysterious item you brought us is actually this!
Be careful. This is a part of advanced technology that destroyed the Ancients.
Got: $I327!
Got: $I344!
Hmm. It appears you don't have all the mysterious parts.
Mysteries still await you somewhere in the world.
This might be the end of the world's mysteries. You've done a great job!
You kids have brought me great joy! I think I will do some relaxing research for a change.
Jibral Castle has been in use since ancient times. Even children must show respect.
See how clean the floors are in the throne room? Tradition has it that cleaning the floor was a punishment.
"We idolize the king. He may be young, but he is a great leader."
"I can't talk about it in the open, but there's a terrible plan afoot in Jibral."
The king cares very deeply about the abnormal occurrences happening here and there.
"No, we're not bored. Although all we do is stand here..."
Don't slip as you run around! This floor is very slippery.
Guests from Talta! The king awaits you.
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
Not used
"Oh, it's the lively children! What are you doing here?"
You're the dog-lover! What about you? What are you doing here in the castle?
"Hey, how rude you are! This person is a grand minister of Jibral."
"It's okay, it's okay. They can't change just because the old man has status now."
"You're a minister? Can you do anything about Talta Village, then?"
"I have seen the reports on Talta, yes. It will take some time, but I will not let anything bad happen."
Please leave it to me and be on your way.
You there! Don't you have business in the basement lab?
The entrance to the basement is the door on the left in the Great Hall.
"If you have business in the lab, use the left-hand door up by the stairs."
"When you go back, say hello to that girl."
There is a strange plant growing in the central garden. Its fruits are like capsules!
"It seems to have been made by the Ancients
Zola! Zola!
Bow to the king!
Nene! Never!
Our mechat is still being researched.
It seems we shouldn't have tried to use those ruined parts.
"Oh, it's you. This mechat still doesn't work."
"If Lady Zola stole a working mechat, we wouldn't need to do these repairs."
How is the mechat that Lady Zola stole? Our repairs are coming along too.
"Near as I can tell, it should be ready to fly in about five years."
Zola's bath... It's already filled.
Zola's towel... It smells nice.
It's lined with cosmetics. It smells... very posh.
