"Something is being displayed, but Shu and the others can't understand it."
This is the elevator switch.
This is the door switch.
I guess we use the $I219 here.
"Okay, here goes!"
Hurry up and use the $I219!
"Shu, use the $I219."
Okay! Okay! I'm working on it!
Use it on that Warp Device over there.
Okay! I said I'm working on it!
Take that!
"""Warp Key description: Healing"""
"After you use the $I219 to activate the Warp Device,"
you'll be able to warp to other locations.
You can also recover from fatigue if you rest at the Warp Device.
You can also recover from fatigue if you rest at the Warp Device.
Do you want to hear more? #Y
Sim
Não
"""Warp Key description: Warping"""
"After you use the Warp Key to activate the Warp Device,"
you can warp to the Device in an instant... 
from any other Warp Device you've activated.
Do you want to hear the description again? #Y
Sim
Não
Thank you for listening. Feel free to use my services again.
"You beat me. I apologize for interfering. Here, take my treasure to make up for it."
Got: $I219
O que é isso?
My apologies. My deepest apologies. Let me explain about this treasure.
This item is a $I219. 
"If you insert a $I219 into a Warp Device, "
you will activate the Warp Device.
You can recover from fatigue if you rest at the Warp Device.
Do you want to hear more? #Y
Sim
Não
There's an even better treasure! The Warp Key Controller.
"It lets you move to the Warp Device from anywhere, "
not just from another Device.
"But I don't have one, so please don't get angry."
That is all I have to explain.
"Oh, and by the way..."
I also unlocked the door to the cockpit. 
"Please forgive me. I'm so, so sorry."
Ir para o 1° andar? #Y
Ir para o 3° andar? #Y
This is the Warp Device. Insert $I219 to activate it.
"Shu, let's use the $I219 on the Warp Device."
Ok.
A tutorial will appear here.
This is the elevator to the first floor.
An indicator needle is moving.
It's already unlocked.
This elevator goes to the 3rd Floor.
It feels like something hot is flowing inside.
This machine looks broken.
Got: $I% x $V%
The cockpit door has been unlocked.
Got: $I% x $V%
"I am so, so sorry."
I will give you every $I219 I have gathered from around the world.
There should be as many Warp Keys as there are Warp Devices:
"23, including this one."
