Leave Upper Mecha Base? #Y
I think we can get it working!
Use the elevator? #Y
It locked!
It's locked.
Got: Security Card for the Lowest Level!
Got: Security Card for the Hangar!
Got: Security Card for the Bridge Waypoint!
Got: Security Card for the Control Room!
Got: Hawk Talon Key!
Cool! This key's shaped like a hawk's talons!
This key might open a treasure chest somewhere in this base.
Cool! This key's shaped like a hawk's talons!
Maybe this key will open a treasure chest somewhere in this base!
It won't open!
It's locked. 
There's a hawk symbol next to the keyhole.
There's a hawk symbol next to the keyhole. 
Use the Hawk Talon Key? #Y
You used the Hawk Talon Key.
The treasure chest opened! 
The security lock activated.
The security lock released.
Hmm... I don't think this security lock is going to release. 
Let's go back down to the floor below and revise our strategy.
All right...
We can't use it. The security lock has activated.
There must be some way to release it...
Go to the 5th Floor? #Y
Go to the 3rd Floor? #Y
