Look! Another Warp Device!
Let's insert a Warp Key there.
I think we can get it working!
"Event. After finding the medicine, Shu and others will go to the Devee village of Lago."
You examined the locker.
There's nothing special.
Hmm? I found something!
It's just trash.
Jiro is excited.
It was just your imagination.
"It's broken, and it no longer runs."
There's nothing but junk here. None of it's even usable.
"Looks like medicines are usually kept here, but nothing looks usable."
This is the door switch.
It's locked.
The Head Doctor's safe opened!
Found $I432 on the bookshelf!
What the...?! We're surrounded!
You used the $I431.
Looks like this was the key for here.
The door unlocked.
It's locked.
It's already unlocked.
Use the $I431? #Y
It won't open!
Maybe there's a mechanism somewhere that will open this door.
"Shu, let's try using the $I431."
Okay.
You examined the Head Doctor's safe.
Use the $I432? #Y
You used the $I432.
I bet we could use that key we found...
