Leave Wire Highlands? #Y
It's a transformation box!
What item do you put in? #Y
Cancel
Iron Amulet 
Soldier's Belt 
Rabbit Gear 
You don't have an Iron Amulet. 
You don't have a Soldier's Belt . 
You don't have a Rabbit Gear. 
You put in an Iron Amulet. 
You put in a Soldier's Belt . 
You put in a Rabbit Gear. 
The transformation box is wriggling around.
The Iron Amulet transformed into a Crystal Amulet!
The Soldier's Belt transformed into a Berserker's Belt!
The Rabbit Gear transformed into a High-speed Gear!
Got: Crystal Amulet 
Got: Berserker's Belt 
Got: High-speed Gear
You can't use that now.
It's a blending box! 
What item do you put in? #Y
Cancel
Wizard's earrings
Mammoth Belt
Realgar Chain
You don't have a wizard's earrings. 
You don't have a Mammoth Belt. 
You don't have a Realgar Chain. 
You put in a wizard's earrings. 
You put in a Mammoth Belt. 
You put in a Realgar Chain. 
What items will you blend? 
Cancel
Nurse Earrings
Magic Anklet 
Cherub Earrings 
You don't have Nurse Earrings. 
You don't have a Magic Anklet. 
You don't have Cherub Earrings. 
You put in Nurse Earrings. 
You put in a Magic Anklet. 
You put in Cherub Earrings. 
The blending box is shuddering. 
The items were blended together into Healer Earrings!
The items were blended together into a Dinosaur Belt!
The items were blended together into a Pearl Rosary!
The items were blended together into a Wizard's Anklet!
The items were blended together into a Knuckle Choker!
The items were blended together into a Gold Amulet!
The items were blended together into a Black Pearl Necklace!
The items were blended together into a Silver Hourglass!
The items were blended together into Silent Breath!
Got: Healer Earrings 
Got: Dinosaur Belt 
Got: Pearl Rosary 
Got: Wizard's Anklet 
Got: Knuckle Choker 
Got: Gold Amulet 
Got: Black Pearl Necklace
Got: Silver Hourglass 
Got: Silent Breath 
"It's a transformation... Hey, wait... This one's different. "
It could be a blending box. 
It blends two items into one. 
Cool! Let's give it a shot! 
"We can only use it once, so let's think carefully about what to put in. "
"Okay, okay. Let's hurry up and try it! "
I don't think he really gets it...
It's a time capsule box! 
What item do you put in? #Y
Cancel
Black Pearl Necklace 
Cherub Earrings 
Realgar Chain
You don't have a Black Pearl Necklace. 
You don't have Cherub Earrings. 
You don't have a Realgar Chain. 
You put in a Black Pearl Necklace. 
You put in Cherub Earrings. 
You put in a Realgar Chain. 
The time capsule box has gone to sleep.
The time capsule box doesn't look like it's ready to open.
The time capsule box is opening!
The Black Pearl Necklace has turned into a Black Jewel Necklace!
The Cherub Earrings have turned into Seraph Earrings!
The Realgar Chain has turned into an Aegirine Chain!
Got: Black Jewel Necklace! 
Got: Seraph Earrings! 
Got: Aegirine Chain! 
Remove the barrier? #Y 
Yes
No
This barrier's really powerful. 
We're in trouble if the barrier fails...
Keep at it! 
How many are there?
Turn it off!
"Hurry, turn it off!"
Yeooww!
Don't do it. Don't turn it off!
