Do you want to use the healing device? #Y
There are three buttons on the treasure chest.
Which button do you press?
Red button
Green button
Yellow button
Cancel
Damn it! It was a trap!
"Oh, crap! Wrong button!"
"Cool, it opened!"
It's locked.
This door is blocked.
Do you want to go up to the 1st Level? #Y
The Eternal Engine here has been removed. Let's go somewhere else.
There's a Machine Gun Crab guarding it.
There's a Tailgunner Robo-Scorpion guarding it.
There's a Flying Mecha Robo guarding it.
... an invader?
You may call me... Silent Ku...
"... my style, my technique... you will die!"
Heh heh heh... So you're the ones that Szabo the master spoke of!
"I'm Turbulent Mai, as wild as the wind! And thanks to you, I'm free again!"
As a token of my gratitude... I'll show you some real fear!
Mwa ha ha! I'll dash you all to bits! Smash and dash into bits and pieces!
"I'm Heat-Wave Sai. I've been locked up too long, and that makes me angry!"
"You, and your friends, and everyone else and their friends, are gonna be blown away!"
The hatch to the Warp Gate is unlocked.
It's already unlocked.
The shutter is sealed up.
There's no response. It seems to be completely blocked.
You get the sense of an imminent danger from just beyond the door.
It's a gigantic cannon. It looks like they plan to use this to attack the castle.
It's a gigantic cannon. It looks like it was used in some ancient battle.
This looks like one of the shells for this cannon.
"The way is blocked by a blue laser, and you can't go any farther."
"The Eternal Engine has stopped, so the laser has shut off."
