Hey! Somebody help!
There's a huge creature there. Can you do anything about it?
A huge creature?
Wh-what's this sound?!
"The sand cloud's this way, right?"
"It gets dangerous from here on, so we'll have to use caution."
Whoa! What the--?! That hole's huge!
What's this hole doing here? It looks pretty deep...
Now ain't the time to chicken out! We'll be fine as long as we don't fall!
"Hey, this tree fell over! Looks like we can climb up."
Something's in here.
Event. A Land Shark in the distance. Shu and the others see the dust from its trail.
They decide to go take a look.
"Wow, you guys are pretty good! "
"I was gonna help you out, though, if you got in a tight spot."
Are you hurt? Everyone back at the Sheep Tribe camp is worried.
"I'm fine. After all, I'm Donpa, the bravest in the camp."
Brave? Um... you really didn't seem all that...
"Anyway, anyway... are you guys going on ahead?"
"Yes. We need to get back to Talta Village, and this is the only way there."
"Oh, I see. Well, I want to thank you. Please take this."
"Besides, I hear a strange growling coming from that hole."
"Well, I want to thank you. Please take this."
"Okay, then, I'm going back to my camp. See you guys later!"
There's a Fat Rat guarding it.
There's a Smirking Scorpion guarding it.
There's a Green Grunt guarding it.
We can't keep going this way. Let's go back to where that drill machine was.
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
