Leave the Ancient Factory? #Y
Ride the conveyor belt? #Y
You didn't find anything.
Yikes!
Phew... 
I already told you... It's gonna take more than raw power.
"Aw, come on, guys. Besides, I think we could take a breather here. "
What? Let's just bust through!
Even mighty warriors need their rest. 
That's right. 
Bah...
Wow! It goes way up there! 
"If we climb this, I'm betting we'll come out on the surface."
Then let's get goin'! 
Okay!
Ugh! Isn't this where that tough robot is?
"Yeah, it is, but maybe we could use that Red Device to neutralize it?"
Noo-trah-laize? You can do that?
Probably... at least in theory.
"I don't really get it, but I'll try anything once!"
Maro too!
It worked!
Wow! Jiro was right!
"Yeah, well, you know..."
There's a Gnashing Imp Trap guarding it.
There's a Double Lance guarding it.
Got: $C4<Broken Barrier Device>!
It's already unlocked.
You can't climb down. The bottom of the ladder is broken off.
It looks like an emergency launch button for a mechat.
There's no response. It seems to be completely blocked.
A burst of cold air blasted out. Everyone's HP went down a little.
