"Oh, I sense a power..."
"Um, did that tree just talk?"
How cool!
Your strange and wondrous power... 
I feel a little of it flowing into me. It is a power that can save this forest.
"If we work together, our power just might be enough to "
save the mad King Ghost.
"Oh, I sense a power..."
Heya! We need your help again!
Whoa!
It looks like this thing is still working.
Turn off the switch? #Y
Yes
No
The poisonous mist cleared up!
The switch is on.
What the heck's that?
A red barrier is blocking the way.
"Okay, time for the Red Device..."
You took out the Red Device.
Destroy the red barrier? #Y
Yes
No
You used the Red Device. 
You destroyed the red barrier!
Wait! This is no ordinary mist! We better be careful!
Hmm? There's something weird about this mist.
It's a transformation box!
What item do you put in? #Y
Epistle of the King Ghost
Cancel
You don't have $I209.
You don't have any medicinal herbs.
You don't have any Antidote.
You put in 99 small stones.
You put in medicinal herbs.
You put in $I209.
The transformation box is wriggling around.
$I209 became $I99!
The medicinal herbs transformed into a Grand Shadow Crystal!
The Antidote transformed into Magical Medicine!
Got: $I44 x 1
Got: Grand Shadow Crystal
Got: Magical Medicine
You can't use that now. 
The Warp Device and controller are reacting!
"""Warp"" is now added to the Main Menu."
What the heck's that dog doing?
Maybe it's looking for bones?
"That's kinda creepy, considering where we are..."
Hmm?! Could that be a $C4<Gabo plant>?!
Could it be?!
Let's have a look!
"All right, now we can save Marumaro's mom and dad!"
"So it was a fake. Well, our only choice is to keep moving forward."
"Okay, Marumaro, let's go!"
Okay!
The tree is withered. An ominous air hangs about. Be careful.
The moss is glowing. It's quite a strange sight. 
The moss is glowing. It's quite a strange sight. 
The moss is glowing. It's quite a strange sight. 
The moss is glowing. It's quite a strange sight. 
Wow! That wheel's taller than a grown man.
Return me... return me... Where is my worldly form?
How long has it been since I was robbed of my soul?
"Hail, traveler! Would you not use that strange and "
wondrous power of yours to find my soul?
Oohh...! That's it! My stolen soul!
How can I ever thank you? I would do anything...
Got: Spirit of the Elder Tree!
The water level in the poison swamp dropped!
There's a Green Skeleton guarding it.
There's a Purple Skeleton guarding it.
There's a Thief Ghost guarding it.
"It pains me to think you retrieved my soul, but I have done so little for you."
Is there anything I could assist you with?
How about telling us where to find a $C4<Gabo plant>?
"A $C4<Gabo plant>, you say? They grow in great numbers deep within the forest."
But how could you possibly get there through this poisonous mist? What a pity.
What are we supposed to do then?
The mist is generated by a machine to the north. Maybe you could stop it.
Return here once the mist clears. I'll tell you where the $C4<Gabo plant> grows.
The mist appears to have cleared. Your power never ceases to amaze me.
"Heh heh heh, nah, it wasn't a big..."
"Sorry, but we don't have much time. Please, tell us where the $C4<Gabo plant> is."
"Oh, yes, of course..."
The $C4<Gabo plants> grow across the bridge near where you found my soul.
You must be careful.
The $C4<Gabo plant>...
There's a Slime Roamer guarding it.
You have obtained a $C4<Gabo plant>. It is a cure-all. Very hard to find these days.
"Now, you'd best forget about this old tree and get that plant to those in need. "
You had best hurry.
Ho ho ho... What use could this old tree be to you?
Hold on!
"What is it, Kluke? We gotta hurry up and collect some plants. "
"This isn't a $C4<Gabo plant>. It looks similar, but it's different from what I saw."
What's with this $C4<Epistle of the King Ghost>?
Hmmm... I have no idea.
The Sheep Tribe can answer questions like these. We should go ask them.
"Okay, let's go pay a visit to the Sheep Tribe Camp."
What's with this$C4<Epistle of the King Ghost>?
Let's head for the Sheep Tribe Camp.
"Shu, let's hurry back to Lago Village!"
"Okay, we could warp there in flash!"
"We're coming, everyone! Hold on!"
The moss looks like it's glowing. You feel strange when you look at it.
"There's a faint red glow. Your MP recovers slightly, but your HP falls a bit."
"There's a bright red glow. Everyone's MP recovers, but their HP falls a bit."
"There's an intense red glow. Your MP recovers, but your HP falls a bit."
"There's an eerie red glow. Your MP recovered, but you're damaged and poisoned."
"Something spurts out of the glowing moss. Your MP recovers, but you smell terrible."
