It won't open!
The power's not on.
"Gah, it won't open!"
It's broken and won't open.
Select a floor. #Y
You arrived at the 2nd Floor.
The power's not on.
I think we can get it working!
Turn on the switch? #Y
You can use the elevator now!
The power for the elevator is on.
What's this?
You found a light stand! 
You found a light stand! 
The lights are on.
You examined the locker.
There's nothing special.
Hmm? I found something!
It's just trash.
Jiro is excited.
It was just your imagination.
"Man, it's dark! I can't see a thing!"
There must be a light switch around here somewhere.
"It's broken, and it no longer runs."
Nothing but junk here. None of it's even usable.
"Looks like medicines are usually kept here, but nothing looks usable."
This is the door switch.
It's a light switch.
Hmm... It won't open.
It doesn't look broken. Maybe there's some sort of trick to it.
3F
1F
Cancel
Do you want to turn on the lights? #Y
This room... Something feels different about it.
This might be the control center for this whole building.
"If it is, then let's check out what's in here."
Gahh!
"Shu, wait! Let's check around a bit more."
You pushed the light switch.
You got the key to the Head Doctor's office.
There's a Medic Maintenancer guarding it.
There's a Wandering Wrath guarding it.
I think we can get in the Head Doctor's office with this key.
I wonder where that office is.
Maybe it was that door we couldn't open earlier.
Let's go take a look.
There wasn't a place like that. Let's look around a little more.
Okay.
This looks like it's the wrong key. Let's try somewhere else.
It looks broken.
It's locked.
It's already unlocked.
It's blocked by a barrier.
It's broken.
The console is already up and running.
"When we leave this room, just turn right and go all the way down the hallway. The Head Doctor's office should be at the very end."
