"My treasure, treasure, treasure!"
You're trying to steal my treasure!
"We use the Warp Key here, right?"
"Okay, here goes!"
Hurry and use the Warp Key!
"Shu, use the Warp Key."
Okay! Okay! I'm working on it!
Use it on that Warp Device over there.
Okay! I said I'm working on it!
It won't open!
I think we can get it to work!
Push the switch? #Y
Yes
No
The hatch is open!
The switch is on.
I think we can get it to work.
Push the switch? #Y
Yes
No
Nothing happened.
It won't open!
It's locked.
"Something is being displayed, but Shu and the others can't understand it."
You've never seen a machine like this before. It's working busily.
This is the elevator switch.
This is the door switch.
Aahhh! You've been sucked into an air vent!
"Welcome, honored customer! "
What are you looking for? Items? Spells? #Y
Items
Accessories
Spells
Cancel
Your business is appreciated! 
Would you like to shop some more? #Y
Yes
No
You're too worried about Kluke and Jiro to fall asleep.
Go to Floor 2A? #Y
Climb in the cockpit? #Y
Leave the Drill Machine? #Y
It's locked.
An indicator needle is moving.
This elevator goes to Floor 2A.
It's locked.
It's already unlocked.
This elevator goes to the cockpit.
You've never seen a machine like this before. It's working busily.
You got machine oil on your hands. You're really stinky...
You almost got sucked in! Everyone's HP has been reduced a bit.
This machine looks broken.
What are you looking for?
Items? Accessories? Spells? #Y
These are the items our masters used.
They should have the same effects on you.
I believe you will like them. They are available for purchase.
How to use the $C1<Sweet Spot>:
"If you stop charging when the $C1<Charge Meter> hits the orange section (the $C1<Sweet Spot>),"
your MP consumption and the time until your next move will be reduced.
"Travelers, I have knowledge to share."
Do you want to learn a combat technique the masters taught me? #Y
The $C1<Charge Meter> displays an orange bar called the $C1<Sweet Spot>. If you stop charging right when the meter reaches the $C1<Sweet Spot>...
Your MP consumption and the time until your next move will be reduced.
