Exit to the outside? #Y
Use the Warp Gate? #Y
You flipped the switch.
It's locked. There's a star mark on the door.
Got: Star Key A
What the?!
There's a Spin-Laser Defender guarding it.
There's a Skeleton General guarding it.
There's an Artillery Robot guarding it.
There's a Fanatic Eye guarding it.
There are three buttons on the treasure chest.
Which button do you press?
Red button
Green button
Yellow button
Cancel
"Ah, dammit! It was a trap!"
"Oh, crap! Wrong button!"
"Cool, it opened!"
Got: Star Key B
It looks like this won't open with just this key.
It's being locked by a sophisticated ancient device.
A section of the sophisticated ancient device has been unlocked.
The sophisticated ancient machine has been unlocked.
There's a Lazy Spine Ghost guarding it.
There's a Dark Poo Snake guarding it.
There's a Bowa-Bowa guarding it.
There's a Riot Puppet guarding it.
There's a Possessed Lizard guarding it.
There's a Flame Gunner guarding it.
There's a Red Infantry guarding it.
