This isn't the way to Talta Village.
Feels like we've missed something...
Let's go back to Talta Village.
Hmm? Hawk Eyes! 
I wonder if they came out because we opened the treasure chest.
Hawk Eyes love shiny things.
Hawk Eyes are really annoying...
Whoa! There're tons of Hawk Eyes here! 
"But there're tons of treasure chests, too! Let's open 'em!"
Be careful! You'll fall if you keep looking down!
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
Be careful! You'll fall if you keep looking down!
Be careful! You'll fall if you keep looking down!
Be careful! You'll fall if you keep looking down!
Be careful! You'll fall if you keep looking down!
It's a fine post.
It's an ancient machine. Don't use it unless you know what you're doing.
It's an ancient machine. Don't use it unless you know what you're doing.
It's an ancient machine. Don't use it unless you know what you're doing.
It's an ancient machine. Don't use it unless you know what you're doing.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's an ancient machine. Don't use it unless you know what you're doing.
It's an ancient machine. Don't use it unless you know what you're doing.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
Be careful! You'll fall if you keep looking down!
It's a fine post.
Be careful! You'll fall if you keep looking down!
Be careful! You'll fall if you keep looking down!
There's a Hawk Eye guarding it.
There's a Shrike Cockatrice guarding it.
Gahh!
Hey! There's a treasure chest over there.
A treasure chest!
I think those birds are guarding it. Maybe there's something good inside.
Hey! A treasure chest just appeared!
It appeared when we defeated that mural monster.
I wonder how it works...
"Hey, something doesn't feel right here. Let's keep going."
I agree.
What's that monster doing? 
Looks like it's searching for something. Wonder if there's something over there. 
Let's finish it off and have a look for ourselves. 
"No, wait! Shu!"
Sorry... Let's look around first. 
I wonder what it was guarding so carefully.
Money. 
"Yep, it was money all right. "
"Birds have a habit of collecting shiny things, so maybe it was trying to get this. "
Hmm... shiny things... 
"Come to think of it, the face on that mural was beautiful. "
Maybe the battle would be easier if we joined together to fight.
"Shu, it's great how you won and all, but don't overdo it. "
Bah. I wonder if he even realizes what he did wrong... 
Look! Another treasure chest just appeared.
Maybe a treasure chest appears when we defeat a mural monster.
Then we should go finish 'em all off!
No! Shu! We don't have time. We have to keep going.
"Oh, yeah. All right."
"Shu, wait."
"Hmm? What is it, Marumaro? "
Over there. Over there.
A treasure chest.
Looks like those birds are guarding it. I bet there's something good inside. 
Let's go see.
"All right, then."
Wait! Shu! 
"I'd like to take a look at that treasure chest, too, but look over there."
That's not the same mural we saw before. We better proceed carefully. 
What the...?! It seems much more powerful than that other mural.
Everyone! Over here!
"What's up, Jiro?"
There're tons of enemies up ahead. We better be careful. 
You're right. 
"So far, it seems like the murals are only along that path over there. "
We have to hurry and move on. This way would probably be faster.
That's true.
There're no murals this way. 
You're right. I just hope it's the right way.
Ah! It's a dead-end! 
I guess we gotta go back to that rope bridge. 
"Well, at least we were able to avoid some battles."
We'll have to pass in front of those murals to get those treasure chests. 
"Shu, wait! "
"Hmm? What's up, Kluke?"
How about we take a break?
Yeah. We've been on our feet a long time. 
"Maro's tired, too! "
"Jiro, do we still have a long way to go? "
Yeah. It'll be a while before we make it out of the valley. 
But there should be a place to rest up ahead. 
"Okay. Let's go just a little farther, guys! "
All right. Let's go. 
Maro right behind ya!
"The bridge was built ages ago, but nothing seems wrong with it."
The bridge looks like it was well built.
