Leave the Ancient Prison? #Y
You didn't find anything.
I think we can get it working!
Push the switch? #Y
The light turned on.
Nothing happened.
The switch is on.
You checked the bed.
You checked the toilet.
You checked inside the snow.
"First off, I've gotta look for everyone."
It won't open!
It's locked.
I'll be back with the key in a jiffy!
"We're counting on you, Shu."
Yeah! Good luck!
Don't go getting yourself killed.
Got: Cell Key (02)
Got: Cell Key (08)
Got: Cell Key (10)
Got: Cell Key (11)
Open the cell door? #Y
The cell door opened.
Close the cell door?
The cell door closed.
Thanks for the help.
Maro been waiting!
Thanks.
It won't open! 
It's locked. 
"First off, why don't we go find everybody?"
It won't open! 
It's locked.
It won't open! 
It's locked. 
Maybe those lamps have something to do with it? 
Hmm... rows of lamps...
It won't open! 
It's locked. 
There's something about the way these lamps are arranged... 
Hmm... the way they're arranged... it's like... 
Hmm...!
Now I see! They're arranged just like the prison cells.
So what does that mean? 
It means there's some sort of connection between the lamps and prison cells! 
Hmm. Interesting... 
"Yeah, interesting!"
The big door can now be opened.
I knew you'd come! I won't give up!
Joined with $P1.
Joined with $P3.
Joined with $P4.
There's no sign of Kluke.
They probably moved her somewhere else.
There's no point sticking around here. Let's make a break for it.
Don't mess with us! We're in a hurry!
What's the rule behind how the lamps are arranged...? Hmm...
Where could the key be? Maybe it fell into the bucket or something.
You checked the bucket.
Is this a prison?
I gotta escape somehow and join up with the others.
Hmm... What's up with this lamp?
Jiro!
Marumaro!
Zola!
Shu!
Hey! How ya doin'!
You all right?
Hmm? What's that?
Hmm... Wonder why it won't open...
The lamps in the middle row are a different color. Maybe it means something.
"The middle row, eh..."
"The middle row, huh..."
You checked the empty can.
Fugitives spotted! Fugitives spotted! Commencing immediate termination!
The key! Just what we needed!
Um... Wasn't the lamps' arrangement related to the prison cells?
"Yes, and there was something peculiar about how the center row was a different color."
It's secured with a solenoid lock.
It's already unlocked.
Looks like... Kluke never used it.
You're covered with a horrible Stink...
It at least looks usable.
It's too thin to protect against this cold.
There's no sign that Zola used it.
It looks pretty worn out.
