I'm coming!
Event. The Drill Machine moves to the Ancient Hospital.
Há diversos dispositivos complexos  posicionados em uma linha.
It has a steering wheel. It looks like you can use it to maneuver.
A needle is moving continuously.
This is the door switch.
This is the elevator switch.
"You tried to turn the wheel, but it was stuck and wouldn't budge."
"A lot of things are being shown, but neither Shu nor anyone can figure it out."
You turned the wheel! But nothing happened.
Ir para o 1° andar? #Y
It's already unlocked.
An indicator needle is moving.
Ancient letters are being displayed on the screen.
Você sente o poder da magia.
This is the elevator to the first floor.
The Drill Machine looks broken.
This machine looks broken.
Nothing is displayed on the screen. It seems broken.
