Sair to the outside? #Y
Use the Warp Gate? #Y
You flipped the switch.
"What--!? Dammit, it won't open."
It doesn't look like it's locked or anything.
It won't open!
It doesn't look like it opens from this side.
This stupid thing won't move!
I bet it needs an activation key of some sort.
You don't have the Key of Spades.
You don't have the key of Clubs.
You don't have the Key of Hearts.
You don't have the Key of Diamonds.
Got: Key of Spades
Got: Key of Clubs
Got: Key of Hearts
Got: Key of Diamonds
It's locked. There's a sun mark on the door.
Got: Sun Key
Yeow!
There's a Wandering Sage guarding it.
There's a Robber Ghost guarding it.
There's a Land-Temple Turtle guarding it.
There's a Blazing Moth guarding it.
Go to the central switch? #Y
There are three buttons on the treasure chest.
Which button do you press?
Red button
Green button
Yellow button
Cancel
"Ah, dammit! It was a trap!"
"Oh, crap! Wrong button!"
"Cool, it opened!"
It's locked. There's a moon mark on the door.
Got: Moon Key
There's an Immortal Wings guarding it.
"It's sealed by the ancient spell ""Solar Eclipse."""
"It's sealed by the ancient spell ""Lunar Eclipse."""
"It's sealed by the powerful ancient spell ""Oblivion."""
The $I% starts to glow.
The $I% starts to glow.
The $I% starts to glow.
The door has been unsealed.
I have a bad feeling about this door.
You mean what's beyond it?
Got: Ancient Emblem - Sun
Got: Ancient Emblem - Moon
Got: Ancient Emblem - Void
There's a Spin-Laser Defender guarding it.
There's a Lazy Spine Ghost guarding it.
There's a Dark Poo Snake guarding it.
There's a Fanatic Eye guarding it.
There's a Bowa-Bowa guarding it.
There's a Riot Puppet guarding it.
There's a Possessed Lizard guarding it.
There's an Artillery Robot guarding it.
There's a Flame Gunner guarding it.
There's a Red Infantry guarding it.
Use the $I%? #Y
