Use the ladders? #Y
It's a transformation box!
What item do you put in? #Y
You don't have $I245.
You don't have $I1.
You don't have $I7.
You put in $I245.
You put in $I1.
You put in $I7.
The transformation box is wriggling around.
$I245 transformed into $I277!
$I1 transformed into $I2!
$I7 transformed into $I8!
Got: $I277
Got: $I2
Got: $I8
You can't use that now. 
Whoa! The bridge...!
I bet we could use this to climb down.
The bridge goes straight down.
That mural just moved! 
It noticed the treasure chest. We better be careful.
That mural just moved! 
No stupid mural's gonna get any of our stuff!
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
Be careful! You'll fall if you keep looking down!
Be careful! You'll fall if you keep looking down!
Be careful! You'll fall if you keep looking down!
Be careful! You'll fall if you keep looking down!
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's an ancient machine. Don't use it unless you know what you're doing.
It's an ancient machine. Don't use it unless you know what you're doing.
It's an ancient machine. Don't use it unless you know what you're doing.
It's an ancient machine. Don't use it unless you know what you're doing.
It's an ancient machine. Don't use it unless you know what you're doing.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
It's a fine post.
Jibral Earrings
Medicine
Shadow Crystal
Cancel
Wha--?
There's a Hawk Eye guarding it.
There's a Ruby Halbird guarding it.
There's a Shrike Cockatrice guarding it.
There's a Pungent Poo Snake guarding it.
Could this be the $I210 the mural was looking for?
Maybe. Let's go give it to him.
You must put five items into this transformation box.
Ruby
Sapphire
Amethyst
Cancel
You don't have $I54.
You don't have enough $I54.
You put in $I54 x 5.
$I54 transformed into $I172!
Got: $I55 x 5
You don't have $I58.
You don't have enough $I58.
Got: $I58 x 5
$I58 transformed into $I75!
Got: $I59 x 5
You don't have $I60.
You don't have enough $I60.
Got: $I60 x 5
$I60 transformed into $I15!
Got: $I61 x 5
Climb down the fallen rope bridge? #Y
Climb up the fallen rope bridge? #Y
It looks like we could use this collapsed rope bridge to climb down.
We could probably go around from the rope bridge on the other side.
I guess we'll just have to go around.
"Oh, man. Not again..."
It looks like it was built before the bridge in the west part of the valley.
"They were built long ago, and some of them look like they could break."
"This bridge is sturdy, and there appears to be no chance it will collapse."
"Hold on, Shu."
What's wrong?
This transformation box isn't like the others.
Really? It looks the same to me.
"With this one, you put in three items to get something new!"
Three items? Let's give it a shot!
You don't have $I%.
You don't have enough $I%.
You put in $I%.
You put in $I% x $V%.
$I% transformed into $I%!
