"Shu, we have to get a $C4<Gabo plant>!"
We gotta hurry up and bring it to the Devee tribe!
"Shu, you forget!"
"There's an eerie red glow. Your MP recovered, but you're damaged and poisoned."
"There's an intense red glow. Your MP recovers, but your HP falls a bit."
"There's a bright red glow. Everyone's MP recovers, but their HP falls a bit."
"There's a faint red glow. Your MP recovers slightly, but your HP falls a bit."
