There is no $I%.
"Dammit, it won't work!"
There must be a way to get it to work. Let's look around somewhere else.
Got: Elevator Key
Use the $I%? #Y
The elevator is now working.
Now we're getting somewhere!
"An elevator! If we use it, we can probably make it farther inside."
We'd better get ourselves in gear and head back to the elevator.
Do you want to go back to the elevator? #Y
It's locked.
"Hey, take a look at that!"
Do you want to go down to the 2nd Level? #Y
There's a Hover Patroller guarding it.
We have to smash the Eternal Engine that's inside! Let's move out!
The shutter is sealed up.
You can't climb down. The bottom of the ladder is broken off.
"It doesn't have a handle, so you can't open it."
It's already unlocked.
