A suspicious-looking mist has risen. You can't proceed any farther.
Hmm? It's getting pretty misty...
The mist is getting really thick! I can't see a thing!
It's dangerous to go any farther in this mist. Let's come back again later.
"Yeah, I guess we have no choice..."
The mist is getting really thick! I can't see a thing!
Maybe we should come another time...
Alumaru Village is nowhere near here!
All the weapons here appear to be ones used by the Gorgo.
