"The sand cloud's this way, right?"
I got a bad feeling about what's ahead...
Looks like we'd better be careful.
"Kluke, you're a girl. You should stay behind us."
"Hey, this tree fell over! Looks like we can climb up."
There's something wrong with this tree.
I think we can push this boulder over...
Huh? There's something here!
"Hey, look! There's a treasure chest!"
Can we get it somehow?
We'll have to think of a way.
There's a Fat Rat guarding it.
There's a Smirking Scorpion guarding it.
There's a Poo Snake guarding it.
There's an Ancient Katydid guarding it.
Jiro! You know what this is?
I'm not sure... it's the first time I've seen anything like it.
"Well, if Jiro doesn't know what it is, we may as well give up."
Hmmm...
"All right, Shu. That's enough out of you."
"And you, too, Jiro. There's no point in worrying about it. Let's just get going."
Isn't this just like what we saw in the ruins?
I think so. It's really strange.
I wonder what it's made of.
You can think about that later. Let's get moving.
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
"The soil is loose, and the trees look sickly. Perhaps there's not enough nutrients?"
