Pegou: $C4<Cristal Hexagonal>!
Wow! Olhe como brilha!
"Maro quer ver,  também!"
É uma forma hexagonal perfeita.
Nunca vi um cristal tão bem formado. Talvez possamos usá-lo para alguma coisa. 
Wow! É um cristal em forma de hexágono! 
Aposto como será útil. Vamos mantê-lo a salvo.
Ei! Talvez possamos usar aquele recife de corais como uma ponte!
Mas está submerso. Não podemos atravessá-lo.
Deve haver uma maneira de atravessar. Vamos voltar para as cavernas e dar outra olhada.
Ei! Talvez possamos usar aquele recife de corais como uma ponte!
O recife de corais está submerso e não pode ser atravessado.
Eu me pergunto se podemos resolver isso... Vamos voltar e dar uma olhada.
"Ei, olhe!"
Huh? O que há com esse barnacle?
Vejam! Ele tem uma boca em forma hexagonal!
Vamos tentar colocar aquele cristal em forma de hexágono nele.
Colocar o $C4<Cristal Hexagonal> no barnacle? #Y
Sim
Não 
Vejam! Ele tem uma boca em forma hexagonal!
"O cristal que encontramos tem a forma de um hexágono, também."
Colocar o $C4<Cristal Hexagonal> no barnacle? #Y
Sim
Não 
Você colocou o $C4<Cristal Hexagonal> no barnacle.
O recife de corais subiu até a superfície!
É um estranho barnacle...
Você encontrou um barnacle com uma boca em formato de hexágono!
Você colocou o $C4<Cristal Hexagonal> no barnacle.
Nós conseguimos atravessar.
"Bom trabalho, Shu!"
Conseguimos!
Yay!
Conseguimos atravessar!
Shu! É uma caixa de transformação!
O que podemos fazer com ela?
"Se você colocar um item aqui, outro diferente vai aparecer!"
Seriously? That's amazing! 
Let's try it out!
This looks like a transformation box. 
"If I remember correctly, you put an item in and out pops a different one."
It's a transformation box!
What item do you put in? #Y
Medicine
Shadow Crystal
Light Crystal
Cancel
You don't have $I1.
You don't have $I7.
You don't have $I4.
You put in $I1.
You put in $I7.
You put in $I4.
The transformation box is wriggling around.
$I1 transformed into $I2!
$I7 transformed into $I8!
$I4 transformed into $I28!
Got: Medicine
Got: High-level Perfume
Got: Grand Shadow Crystal
You can't use that now. 
Hey! That's a scab barnacle! They're extremely rare!
Really?! Let's go check it out!
Look! That's a scab barnacle! They're really hard to find. 
Let's go take a look!
Hmm? What're those? Looks like a big group pf some sort...
I think those are Hermit Crab Poos...
What are those?
They use poos instead of shells to live in.
"But the truth is, they'd rather have armor instead. Or so I've heard..."
"Jiro, you know a little about these things, don't you? "
"Hermit Crab Poos tend to act in groups, right? "
Isn't that what you said? It's not like I care or anything!
Got: Fish-shaped Key!
"Wow, neat! This key's shaped like a fish!"
This key just might open a treasure chest somewhere in these caverns.
"Wow, neat! This key's shaped like a fish!"
I bet it opens a treasure chest or something here in these caverns!
It won't open!
It's locked.
There's a fish mark next to the keyhole.
"Shu, maybe we could use that key we found?"
Use the $C4<Fish-shaped Key>? #Y
Yes
No
You used the $C4<Fish-shaped Key>.
The treasure chest opened! 
Got (item name).
There's a Hermit Crab Poo guarding it.
There's a Magic Jellyfish guarding it.
Hmm?
That barnacle has a hexagon-shaped mouth.
Look at this fish mark next to the keyhole.
A refreshing scent comes wafting out. You recovered some HP.
A weird bug came out and bit you. You took a little damage.
Something comes spraying out. The smell is gone.
A refreshing scent comes wafting out. Everyone recovered some HP.
A fishy smell comes flooding out. You're covered in an awful smell...
The coral in this cavern glows.
It looks like something is inside the barnacle.
