Leave the Aurora Ruins? #Y
"Uh, hey there."
"While you're here, I have a favor to ask."
"As you are traveling, can you collect any Aurora Droplets you happen upon?"
I have a feeling that if I have more Aurora Droplets I'll be able to collect better items.
"That is, if you feel like it. Much obliged."
Thanks for keeping the Aurora Droplets in mind!
"Oh, hey there. Thanks again. You should take a look at what I've found."
"Oh, hey there. Thanks again. You should take a look at what I've found."
"Please, help me!"
"Hey, isn't that Mr. Aurora? What are you doing here?"
"I'm saved! Thank you, thank you."
I came here to the Aurora Ruins using the Aurora Droplets you gave me.
"I was so excited by the discovery, suddenly the earth began to shake."
"Then the monsters appeared. As you saw, I was captured."
"Okay then, I'm going to give you a great deal on these special items!"
"Shu, is that..."
It's already unlocked.
Gas leaks from the pipes. Now you smell bad.
Fresh air wafts from the pipes. It's a nice odor.
Hey! Isn't that the $I169?
"Yes, but..."
"Oh I see. You fellas want the autograph of the famous adventurer, Toripo."
"Well, that's..."
Usually I decline such requests.
"But since you saved me from the monsters, and I probably couldn't have made it here without you..."
"I'll make an exception. Here, give that to me."
He took $I169.
Hey!
Whew. Done!
$I170 received.
...
What? Are you speechless with joy?
You can make that your family heirloom. Take good care of it!
You can see the autograph from the Item Record!
