Do you want to use the healing device? #Y
There are three buttons on the treasure chest.
Which button do you press?
Red button
Green button
Yellow button
Cancel
Dammit! It was a trap!
"Oh, crap! Wrong button!"
"Cool, it opened!"
Wha--?
"Shu, let's go back."
"Unless we do something about this poison mist, we can't get inside."
I wonder what this switch does.
Press and see!
"Oh, Marumaro!"
What? What? What's goin' on?
It looks like it's some sort of air ventilation system inside the ship.
That's no fun.
It's locked.
This door is blocked.
You've been paralyzed.
Do you want to go to 1st Level? #Y
Do you want to go to the 3rd Level? #Y
There's a Tailgunner Robo-Scorpion guarding it.
There's a Flying Mecha Robo guarding it.
You don't have the key to operate this elevator.
"Dammit, it won't work!"
"We need a key for this, too... Oh well, I guess we'll have to look for it."
Got: Elevator Key
The Eternal Engine here has been removed. Let's go somewhere else.
Push the switch? #Y
Hmm? Do you smell that? It's like the faint odor of something poisonous
"Well, the poison mist is fading, thanks to that ventilation switch we used earlier."
"Yeah, Maro Hero!"
"Yeah, yeah."
